

# **DHANU SATRIO DARJANTO**

+62-81298063349

satriodhanu12@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/dhnstr/

Bandung, 10 January 2002

#### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor Degree in Informatics

## **Telkom University** 2020 - present

- Participant at GEMASTIK XIV Competitive Programming (Aug 2021)
- Creating an alien invasion game in
- Developing Simple Learning Management System in Python.
- Building a program with Genetic Algorithm in Python

# Senior High School SMAN 3 Bekasi 2017 - 2020

• The organizing committee of the SMAN 3 Bekasi's birthday event

#### **SKILLS**

- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Problem Solving
- Programming
- Analytical Skills
- Python
- Java
- CSS
- HTML

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am currently a last-year informatics student, future mobile and web developer. I am very interested in the world of technology, especially in a mobile applications. My passion for mobile application brought me to Telkom University. For the last 3 years, I studied many programming languages such as Python, Golang, and C++ to improve my problem-solving skill. Now I am currently being active as a practice assistant in Computer Network and Operating System course. being a lecturer assistant is an honor because it will improve my experience, time management skills, and discipline.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Mathematic Discrete Asistant Lecturer

Jun 2022 - Sept 2022

#### Telkom University I Bandung

- Conducting task evaluation and summarization.
- Performing testing on online quiz questions.
- Assisting and answering student questions on an online forum.

Practicum Assistant for Computer Network

Mar 2023 - Jun 2023

#### Telkom University I Bandung

- · Conducting assessments on laboratory journals.
- · Explaining laboratory materials.
- Providing assistance to students during major assignments.

Practicum Assistant for Operating System

Mar 2023 - Jun 2023

#### Telkom University I Bandung

- · Conducting assessments on laboratory journals.
- · Explaining laboratory materials.
- Providing assistance to students during major assignments.

## ORGANIZATION

PANDA FIF Telkom University

Jan 2022 - Jan 2023

Telkom University I Bandung

PB Saturday Morning

Jan 2018 - present

**Bekasi** 

Member Badminton Community

Informatics Laboratory

Mar 2023 - present

Telkom University I Bandung